Help!
Please let me go!
Do you want money?
My dad is very rich.
I'll give you lots and lots of money.
Please let me go!
Does your dad have a lot of money?
Is he richer than me?
What do you want?
What do I want?
Out in the middle of nowhere,
just a man and a woman...
What do you think I want?
Help!
Stop struggling!
So damn annoying.
Grey Wolf.
Are you kidding me?!
I'm from Yan Li's hometown!
You can't kill me!
How dare you touch the Boss's woman?
You've got a death wish!
Dispose of the body.
Drive.
That bastard Yan Li
tells me to do a job,
but gives me no money,
and no car.
Bro.
Let me borrow your car.
No way.
You got a worm tattoo.
What are you so cocky about?
Are you sure this is the place?
I'm sure.
This is where the organization does its dirty work.
Stop right there!
The scene is cordoned off.
Unauthorized personnel, step back.
My daughter is in there!
Family members are not allowed either.
You cannot interfere with a police investigation.
It wasn't me!
Sun Ming!
Go.
You two, come here.
Let's go.
Did you find her?
Our criminal investigators
did not find the victim or the kidnappers at the scene.
However, they did find some bloodstains.
We cannot confirm yet if they belong to the victim.
What about the smartwatch?
Is there still a signal?
We cannot track it anymore.
Come on, you guys are moving way too slow!
Hurry up, will you?
Gu Yan, I completely understand how you feel right now.
But when it comes to finding someone,
leave it to the police.
Just calm down.
That's my own daughter!
How can I not panic?
Just calm down!
Gu Ting is what matters right now.
Finding her is the priority, okay?
Calm down, my ass!
Tingting hasn't had a single good day since she met you!
But saving Gu Ting is the priority right now!
But we can't even find her now!
Enough, Gu Yan.
You need to
provide a recent photo of Gu Ting.
The clearer, the better.
I don't have her photo on my phone.
I have some at home.
Just think of what Yaoyao looks like,
and you'll know what Gu Ting looks like.
What do you mean?
Who?
Yaoyao is my biological sister.
And Li Wen's fiancée.
That's why you got close to my daughter, isn't it?
You bastard!
I'll kill you!
Gu Yan!
Li Wen!
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
I can explain later.
But saving Gu Ting is the most important thing right now.
Every minute we delay could cost her her life.
You...
Are you out of your mind?
He's a cop!
You're assaulting an officer!
Do you realize that?
I can't let them take me away now.
Once I find Tingting,
I'll turn myself in.
Sun Ming!
Think carefully.
Who else could've told Gu Ting your true identity?
Who sent you this?
Never mind who sent it.
When my daughter showed me the chat logs,
I was in a rush and didn't pay attention.
Now I remember.
That contact name
seemed to be
Mr. Yan.
All right. Got it.
This Gu Yan...
He's really ruthless.
Captain.
The information you asked for.
Read it.
Yan Li.
Originally an external expert at the medical university,
and a psychology counselor.
His family does not own any major businesses.
His other identity is
the controller of the Tucun Enclosed Building.
Enclosed buildings again.
What are the results of the local station's investigation so far?
Captain,
because the sheer number is too large,
the investigation will take a bit more time.
From now on,
Yan Li's whereabouts
and all assets under his name
must be closely monitored.
Yes, Captain.
If I am not mistaken,
Yan Li is highly likely the boss behind the scenes.
Xiaolin said he took advantage of the numerous enclosed buildings
and the excellent cover they provide,
so he must be prepared.
Ordinary methods might not work.
You should not get involved in this anymore.
Let the police handle it.
Hold on.
We've come this far, and you're telling me...
Cases must follow procedure.
You are not a cop.
You cannot participate.
It puts me in a tough spot.
Fine.
Then promise me,
you will find out the truth about Yaoyao's death.
Who are you?
Go wash up.
Then put this on.
What do you want?
You are a gift from heaven.
I am taking it back now.
Is that not reasonable?
What do you mean?
You're a psycho!
Let go of me!
I cannot do that.
You are mine.
From now on,
you will live here
as my
private property.
You're insane!
This place
is completely sealed off.
The soundproofing is excellent.
Screaming will do you no good.
You had better behave.
Why does your voice sound so familiar?